<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrawlEO!</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrawler">Scrawler</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrawlers">Scrawlers</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrapers">Scrapers</string>
    <string name="title_activity_new_scrawler">Create new Scrawler</string>
    <string name="title_activity_edit_scrawler">Edit Scrawler</string>

    <string name="page_title">Title</string>
    <string name="title_activity_page">Page</string>

    <!-- from https://seositecheckup.com/seo-audit/java.meritcampus.com -->

    <string name="page_meta_title">Title</string>
    <string name="page_meta_title_content">The meta title of your page has a length of 87 characters. Most search engines will truncate meta titles to 70 characters. </string>
    <string name="page_meta_title_help">Your page\'s meta title is an HTML tag that defines the title of your page. This tag displays your page title in search engine results, at the top of a user\'s browser, and also when your page is bookmarked in a list of favorites. A concise, descriptive title tag that accurately reflects your page's topic is important for ranking well in search engines.</string>

    <string name="page_meta_description">Description</string>
    <string name="page_meta_description_help">Your page\'s meta description is an HTML tag that is intended to provide a short and accurate summary of your page. Search engines use meta descriptions to help identify the a page\'s topic - they may also use meta descriptions by displaying them directly in search engine results. Accurate and inviting meta descriptions can help boost both your search engine rankings and a user's likelihood of clicking through to your page.</string>
    <string name="page_meta_description_content">The meta description of your page has a length of 156 characters. Most search engines will truncate meta descriptions to 160 characters. </string>

    <string name="page_h1">h1</string>
    <string name="pahe_h1_help">Check if any H1 headings are used in your page. H1 headings are HTML tags that are not visible to users, but can help clarify the overall theme or purpose of your page to search engines. The H1 tag represents the most important heading on your page, e.g., the title of the page or blog post.  </string>
    <string name="page_h1_content">Your page contains H1 headings. Their contents are listed below: </string>
</resources>
